<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dane Jeon</title>
    <description>Hello everyone! Welcome to my website! I upload both about my daily and academic life. 
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 10:13:18 +0900</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 10:13:18 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Possible Future Posts</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Me being the nerd that I am, a lot of the posts that I’ll upload will be on topics within academia. The whole website will be focused more on diversity rather than depth and perfection, well justifiably; I mean, I’m only a undergraduate student (If I’d actually know some stuff, I’d publish a book haha). I note here some topics that I’ll very likely write stuff on in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Medicene and Biology&lt;/strong&gt; Recently, I’ve grown a huge interest in medicene and the human body in general. I’m having a hard time trying to grasp, being blatently honest, any topic within the subject, so this will perhaps take some time and effort before posting. If I can, I’ll try to add some mathematical, physical, or computational flare, but this is a hope, not a certainty. There has been too many directions of approach to the subject: biochemistry, neurochemistry, modelling, anatomy, physiology, pharmacology (pretty much the syllabus of USMLE at this point haha). I’ll take my time for this.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Psychology and Ethics&lt;/strong&gt; This has been a interest of mine that has been sustained for a long period of time. I really miss the times that I actually read and studied the ideas of different philosophers (I mean, you can just look at the footer of the website), and I just might get at it.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Physics and Mathematics&lt;/strong&gt; I mean, this I have &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;too&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; much to study and write about. Perhaps it’s exactly why I’m studying the damn thing haha. Topics that have recently interested me have been differential forms, and to an extension, manifolds and differential geometry, fluid dynamics, general relativity, analysis, and etcetera. I have a lot of sources that I can refer to in my disposal, and recently, I’ve been feeling so blessed about it. Differential forms by Tao, fluids by Chorin, relativity by Carroll?! Gosh I’m rich. You should really look forward to it.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My usual good bye message would be “see y’all”, but today, for the heck of it, I’ll try this one out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheers!!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/academia/2024/04/12/post-types-for-future-reference.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/academia/2024/04/12/post-types-for-future-reference.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Academia</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to my Website!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi friends and family! This is the first article in my website. I’m still working on the whole thing, so please don’t expect alot for the first few months. While the whole thing is working out, you should really check out my &lt;strong&gt;about&lt;/strong&gt; page. It has a short description of who I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m also planning to write a lot of academic posts, for archiving and etcetera. My most recent interest lies in a topic called &lt;strong&gt;differential forms&lt;/strong&gt;. I mean, what’s life without a daily dose of new maths? So here’s a cool equation for y’all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;font-size:150%;&quot;&gt;
$$\int_{M}d\omega=\int_{\partial M}\omega$$
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just so you know, it’s called the &lt;strong&gt;generalised Stokes’ theorem&lt;/strong&gt;. One of my favorites at the moment!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/me/2024/04/10/welcome-to-my-website.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/me/2024/04/10/welcome-to-my-website.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Me</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
